export default [
{
    question:"1st quistion",
    options:["option1","option2","option3","option4"],
    answer:1,
},
{
    question:"2st quistion",
    options:["option1","option2","option3","option4"],
    answer:3,
},
{
    question:"3st quistion",
    options:["option1","option2","option3","option4"],
    answer:2,
},
{
    question:"4st quistion",
    options:["option1","option2","option3","option4"],
    answer:3,
},
{
    question:"5st quistion",
    options:["option1","option2","option3","option4"],
    answer:0,
},
{
    question:"6st quistion",
    options:["option1","option2","option3","option4"],
    answer:1,
},
{
    question:"7st quistion",
    options:["option1","option2","option3","option4"],
    answer:3,
},
{
    question:"8st quistion",
    options:["option1","option2","option3","option4"],
    answer:2,
},
{
    question:"9st quistion",
    options:["option1","option2","option3","option4"],
    answer:3,
},
{
    question:"10st quistion",
    options:["option1","option2","option3","option4"],
    answer:0,
}



];